Stafford, Ronald B.; Papers apap217
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Letters of Support, 1993-2002; Undated; 8; 5.0 cubic ft.
  - Town of Thurman, Veterans Memorial Park, 1999 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 54)
  - Town of Westport, Clean Water Act Grant, 1999 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 55)
  - Tupper Lake Central School, Goals 2000 Grant, 1999 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 56)
  - Tupper Lake Central School, Target Instructional Staff Development Grant, 1999 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 57)
  - Village of Greenwich, Greenwich Community Center, 1999 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 58)
  - Village of Hudson Falls, Housing Improvement Program, 1999 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 59)
  - Village of Lake Placid, Bike/Ped Transportation Path, 1999 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 60)
  - Village of Saranac Lake, Saranac River Walk, 1999 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 61)
  - Warren and Hamilton Counties Community Action Agency, Hunger Prevention and Nutrition Assistance Program Grant, 1999 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 62)
  - Warren County Soil and Water Conservation District, Warrensburg Recreation Field, 1999 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 63)
  - Warren-Washington Homeless Youth Coalition, 1999 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 64)
  - Washington County Economic Opportunity Council, HOME and RESTORE, 1999 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 65)
  - Whitehall Skene Manor Preservation, Inc. Historic Preservation Project Fund, 1999 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 66)
  - Wiswall Center for Independent Living, Freedom Park, 1999 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 67)
  - Adirondack Community Action Program (ACAP), Child Care Resource and Referral Program, 2000 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 68)
  - Adirondack Community Action Program (ACAP), Early Head Start Program in Essex County, 2000 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 69)
  - Adirondack Community Action Program (ACAP), Moriah and Willsboro Central School Districts After-School Programs, 2000 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 70)
  - Catholic Charities of the Diocese of Ogdensburg, Senior Companion Project, 2000 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 71)
  - Chazy After School Program, Youth Development Plan, 2000 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 72)
  - City of Glens Falls, Affordable Home Ownership Development Program, 2000 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 73)
  - City of Glens Falls, McEchron House, 2000 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 74)
  - City of Glens Falls, Brownfields Assessment Demonstration Pilots Program, 2000 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 75)
  - City of Glens Falls, HOME Program Grant, 2000 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 76)
  - City of Plattsburgh, Farmers' Market Grant, 2000 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 77)
  - City of Plattsburgh, Waterfront Rediscovery Award, 2000 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 78)
  - City of Plattsburgh, Governor's Waterfront Rediscovery Award, 2000 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 79)
  - City of Plattsburgh, Heritage Trail Recreational Path, 2000 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 80)
  - City of Plattsburgh/Clinton County, Lake Champlain Floating Boardwalk Project, 2000 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 81)
  - City of Plattsburgh, Comprehensive Downtown Revitalization Program, 2000 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 82)
  - ComLink, HOME Program Grant, 2000 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 83)
  - Essex Community Heritage Organization, Homebuyer Assistance Program, 2000 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 84)
  - Extension of Natural Gas Service to Clinton, Franklin, and St. Lawrence Counties, 2000 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 85)
  - Franklin County, Empire Zone Designation, 2000 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 86)
  - Franklin County, Microenterprise Assistance Program, 2000 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 87)
  - Fort Ticonderoga, Historic Preservation Project, East Flank Wall, 2000 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 88)
  - Glens Falls Association for the Hearing Impaired, 2000 (Box 3 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 89)
  - Green Mountain Development Group, Cedars Senior Living Community, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 1)
  - Homefront Development Corporation, HOME Program Grant, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 2)
  - Legal Aid Society of Northeastern New York, Domestic Violence Legal Assistance Project, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 3)
  - Pride of Ticonderoga, Inc. HOME Program Grant, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 4)
  - Homefront Development Corporation, Rural Housing Assistance Program, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 5)
  - Lake George Visitors Expo Center, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 6)
  - Lower Adirondack Regional Arts Council (LARAC) Lapham Carriage House, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 7)
  - North Country Behavioral Healthcare Network, Rural Health Outreach Program, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 8)
  - Plattsburgh-North Country Chamber of Commerce, On-The-Job Training Program, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 9-10)
  - Pride of Ticonderoga, Inc. Municipal Park Project, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 11)
  - Rural Health Training Center, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 12)
  - Sagamore Institute, Historic Preservation Project, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 13)
  - Shukla, Dr. Kalpesh, J-1 Visa Waiver, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 14)
  - Town of Argyle, Municipal Park Project, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 15)
  - Town of Ticonderoga, Community Development Block Grant, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 16)
  - Town of Constable, Small Cities Community Development Block Grant, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 17)
  - Town of Fort Ann, Municipal Park Project, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 18)
  - Town of Fort Edward, D & H Station Renovation, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 19)
  - Town of Fort Edward, Master Plan Revision, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 20)
  - Town of Johnsburg, First Wilderness Heritage Corridor, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 21)
  - Town of Johnsburg, Ski Bowl Park, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 22)
  - Town of Keene, Riverside Park and Walkway, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 23)
  - Town of Lewis, Small Cities Community Development Block Grant, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 24)
  - Town of Plattsburgh, Wallace Hill Sewer District #1, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 25)
  - Town of Morehouse, Municipal Park Project, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 26)
  - Town of North Elba, Housing Rehabilitation Program, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 27)
  - Town of Schroon, Lakefront park, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 28)
  - Town of Ticonderoga, Frazier Bridge, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 29)
  - Town and Village of Granville, Municipal Park Project Funding, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 30)
  - Tupper Lake Central School, Goals 2000 Grant (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 31)
  - Village of Hudson Falls, HOME Program Grant, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 32)
  - Village of Keeseville, Veterans Memorial Park, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 33)
  - Village of Port Henry, Sewer System Rehabilitation, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 34)
  - Village of Port Henry, Champlain Valley Heritage Network, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 35)
  - Village of Rouses Point, Local Waterfront Revitalization Program, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 36)
  - Warren County, Empire Zone Designation, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 37)
  - Warren County, Strengthening Community Resources Program, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 38)
  - Warren-Hamilton Counties Community Action Agency, Nutrition Outreach and Education Program Funds, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 39)
  - Washington County Head Start-Early Head Start Program, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 40)
  - Washington County District Attorney's Office, Washington County Rural Crimes Task Force, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 41)
  - Whiteface Preservation and Resource Association, National Register of Historic Places, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 42)
  - Willsboro Senior Housing Corporation, HOME Program Grant, 2000 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 43)
  - Adirondack Community Action Program, After-School Program, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 44)
  - Adirondack Park Agency, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 45)
  - Adirondack Kitchen Project-New York StateERDA Grant, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 46)
  - Adirondack Kitchen Project, Value-Added Agricultural Product Market Development Grant, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 47)
  - Adirondack North Country Association (ANCA), Tupper Lake Trails, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 48)
  - Battle of Plattsburgh Association, Historic Preservation Project Funding, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 49)
  - Behavioral Health Services North, Inc., Domestic Violence Shelter, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 50)
  - Bob Venne Park, Inc. Municipal Park Project Funding, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 51)
  - Bolton Free Library, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 52)
  - City of Glens Falls, McEchron House Renovation, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 53)
  - City of Plattsburgh, Dock Street Landing and Waterfront Park Project, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 54)
  - City of Plattsburgh, Rail Yard Waterfront Rediscovery Program, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 55)
  - ComLinks Franklin County, West Valley II Townhouse, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 56)
  - Clean Water/Clean Air Bond Act and Environmental Protection Fund, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 57)
  - Essex County Industrial Development Agency, Small Cities Micro Business Program Grant, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 58)
  - Federal Transportation Enhancements Program (TEP), 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 59)
  - Food and Agricultural Research and Development Grant Program, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 60)
  - Fort Hudson Health Services Corporation Daycare Center, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 61)
  - Fort Ticonderoga Association, South Terreplein Wall Rehabilitation, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 62)
  - Friends of the North Country, Inc. Keeseville Barn Restoration, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 63)
  - Friends of the North Country, Inc. Small Cities Community Development Block Grant (7 Cities), 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 64)
  - Franklin County, Empire Zones Program, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 65)
  - Greater Adirondack Resource Conservation and Development Council - Global Export Market Service Grant, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 66)
  - Green Mountain Development Group, Cedars Senior Living Community, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 67)
  - Herkimer County Area Development Corporation, Southern Adirondack Trail, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 68)
  - Holmquist Barn Restoration, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 69)
  - HomeFront Development Corporation, Ranson Stiles House, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 70)
  - Homeless Housing Assistance Program Funds, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 71)
  - Lake Placid-Essex County Visitors Bureau, Lake Champlain Visitor's Center, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 72)
  - Local Waterfront Revitalization Program Funding, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 73)
  - New York State Housing Trust Fund Corporation (HTFC) Programs, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 74)
  - North Country Housing Rehabilitation Program, Clinton County, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 75)
  - North Country Behavioral Healthcare Network, Adventure Based Counseling Program, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 76)
  - Oak Mountain Ski Area, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 77)
  - Plattsburgh-North Country Chamber of Commerce, Occupational Safety and Health Training and Education Program, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 78)
  - Pride of Ticonderoga, HOME Funding, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 79)
  - Pyramids Preschool Services, Plattsburgh Daycare Center, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 80)
  - Richards Library, Historic Preservation Project Funding, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 81)
  - Sagamore Institute, Sagarmore Great Camp Renovation, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 82)
  - St. Luke's Episcopal Church, Stained Glass Window Rehabilitation, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 83)
  - Thomas Shipman Sr. Memorial Youth Center, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 84)
  - Three Falls Walking Trail, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 85)
  - Town of Chazy, Municipal Park Project Funding, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 86)
  - Town of Essex, Old Stone Church Restoration, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 87)
  - Town of Fort Edward, Veterans Memorial, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 88)
  - Town of Fort Ann, Town Park, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 89)
  - Town of Johnsburg, Ski Bowl Park, 2001 (Box 4 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 90)
  - Town of Moriah Historical Society "Mineville", 2001 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 1)
  - Town of Plattsburgh, Small Cities Community Development Block Grant, 2001 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 2)
  - Town of Jay, HUD Grant, 2001 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 3)
  - Town of Harrietstown, Old Lake Colby Road Housing Rehabilitation Program, 2001 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 4)
  - Tupper Lake Chamber of Commerce, Spruce Park Street Project, 2001 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 5)
  - Town of Lake Pleasant, Lake Pleasant Park Sewer Service, 2001 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 6)
  - Town of Lake Pleasant, Recreational Trails, 2001 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 7)
  - Town of Moira, HOME Program Grant, 2001 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 8)
  - Town of Newcomb Municipal Park Project, 2001 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 9)
  - Town of Plattsburgh, Public Park on Lake Champlain, 2001 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 10)
  - Town of Keene, Ausable River East Branch Park, 2001 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 11)
  - Tupper Lake Central School, Tri-Lakes Center for Instructional Technology Training, 2001 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 12)
  - Village of Dannemora, Recreational Park, 2001 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 13)
  - Village of Dannemora, Municipal Park Project, 2001 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 14)
  - Village of Lake Placid, Bandshell Park Rehabilitation, 2001 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 15)
  - Village of Keeseville, Municipal Park Funding, 2001 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 16)
  - Village of Keeseville, Veterans Memorial Park, 2001 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 17)
  - Village of Tupper Lake, Local Waterfront Revitalization Plan, 2001 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 18)
  - Village of Rouses Point, Multimodal Lakefront Facility, 2001 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 19)
  - Village of Fort Edward, Housing Improvement Program, 2001 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 20)
  - Village of Fort Edward, Small Cities Grant, 2001 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 21)
  - Village of Granville, Local Law Enforcement Block Grant, 2001 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 22)
  - Village of Hudson Falls, Small Cities Community Development Block Grant, 2001 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 23)
  - Village of Lake Placid, Bandshell Park, 2001 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 24)
  - Village of Saranac Lake, Algonquin Avenue Water Line, 2001 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 25)
  - Warren-Hamilton County Housing Corporation, 2001 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 26)
  - Adirondack Community Action Programs, Ticonderoga International Care Facility, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 27)
  - Adirondack Vets House, Inc., 26 Pine Street Property, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 28)
  - Allenwaite Farms, Inc., New York StateERDA Grant for Dairy Waste Management, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 29)
  - Cambridge Valley Community Development and Preservation Partnership. Hubbard Block Rural Retail Commercial Revitalization and Development Project, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 30)
  - Cambridge Fire Department, Acquisition of New Fire Equipment, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 31)
  - Champlain Valley Physicians Hospital Medical Center, Expansion of Cardiac Services, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 32)
  - Chapman Historical Museum, DeLong House Restoration, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 33)
  - Chilson Fire Department, New Pump Acquisition, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 34)
  - Charitable Gaming Registration Number 8, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 35)
  - City of Glens Falls, Acquisition, Rehab, Resale Program, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 36)
  - City of Glens Falls, Glens Falls Civic Center, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 37)
  - City of Plattsburgh, Rail Yard Waterfront Rediscovery Program, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 38)
  - City of Plattsburgh, Lake Champlain Shoreline Acquisition, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 39)
  - City of Plattsburgh, Senior Homeowners Rehabilitation Program, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 40)
  - Clinton County, S.T.O.P. Violence Against Women, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 41)
  - Development Corporation of Clinton County, Banker Road Industrial Park, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 42)
  - Division of Housing and Community Renewal, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 43)
  - Empire State Development Corporation, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 44)
  - Essex County Industrial Development Agency, Micro Enterprise Assistance Program, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 45)
  - Essex County Heritage Organization, Homebuyer Assistance Program, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 46)
  - Essex County Industrial Development Agency, Micro Enterprise Assistance Program, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 47)
  - Fort Hudson Health Services, Nursing Home Quality Improvement Demonstration Program Funding, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 48)
  - Fort Ticonderoga Association, MARS Education Center, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 49)
  - Fort Ticonderoga Association, South Wall Rehabilitation, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 50)
  - Franklin County Industrial Development Agency, Chateaugay Business Park, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 51)
  - Franklin County Industrial Development Agency, Wood Products Business Incubator Facility at Paul Smith's College, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 52)
  - Franklin County, Jobs Access and Reverse Commute Program Grant, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 53)
  - Friends of Lyon Mountain, Inc., Lyon Mountain Mining and Railroad Museum, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 54)
  - Friends of North Country, Barn Restoration and Preservation Programs, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 55)
  - Friends of North Country, Clinton County Home Improvement Program, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 56)
  - Friends of North Country, Franklin County Home Improvement Program, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 57)
  - Friends of North Country, Keeseville Waterfront Revitalization, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 58)
  - Glens Falls YMCA, Parks Development Program Grant, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 59)
  - Hamilton County, Empire Zone Designation, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 60)
  - Hamilton County, Small Cities Community Development Block Grant, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 61)
  - HomeFront Development Corporation Affordable Home Ownership Development Program Grant, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 62)
  - HomeFront Development Corporation, Argyle Senior Housing, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 63)
  - Housing Trust Fund Corporation (HTFC), 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 64)
  - Inlet Volunteer House Company New Rescue Truck Acquisition, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 65)
  - International Paper's Empire Opportunity Fund, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 66)
  - Lake George Venture Partners LLC, Lake George Forum - 504 Loan, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 67)
  - Lake George Venture Partners LLC, Lake George Forum, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 68)
  - Legal Aid Society of Northeastern New York, Domestic Violence Legal Assistance Project, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 69)
  - New York State HOME Program Grant, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 70)
  - North Creek Townhouses, HOME Funding, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 71)
  - Raquette Lake Fire Department, New Tanker/Pumper Acquisition, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 72)
  - Salem Dairy Farmer Group, Salem Cattle Manure Treatment Project, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 73)
  - Smith, Kevin - Fort Edward Grocery Store, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 74)
  - Small Cities Application, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 75)
  - St. Luke's Episcopal Church, Stained Glass Windows Rehabilitation, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 76)
  - Town of Beekmantown, Housing Rehabilitation and Replacement Program, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 77)
  - Town of Black Brook Fern Lake Study, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 78)
  - Town of Black Brook Housing Rehabilitation and Replacement Program, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 79)
  - Town of Chateaugay Small Cities Community Development Block Grant, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 80)
  - Town of Fort Edward Community Development Strategic Plan, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 81)
  - Town of Fort Edward Patriotic Garden, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 82)
  - Town of Fort Edward, U.S. Route 4 Corridor Management Plan, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 83)
  - Town of Fort Edward Water District Extensions, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 84)
  - Town of Malone Housing Rehabilitation Program, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 85)
  - Town of Minerva Donnelly Beach Improvement Project, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 86)
  - Town of Moira HOME Program Grant, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 87)
  - Town of Plattsburgh, South Plattsburgh Water System, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 88)
  - Town of Schroon/Oscar Seagle Association - Seagle Music Colony, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 89)
  - Town of Ticonderoga Small Cities Community Development Block Grant, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 90)
  - Town of Wells Handicapped-Accessible Fishing Deck, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 91)
  - Tupper Lake, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 92)
  - Village of Dannemora, Recreational Park, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 93)
  - Village of Fort Edward, Housing Improvement Program, 2002 (Box 5 (8-Letters of Support), Folder 94)